# LoganAlleyne

### Web Developer & Designer

#### Contact\_\_\_



BN1



Please get in contact via my website



loganalleyne. com

### About

I'm a Web Developer & Designer, passionate about creating clean, meaningful, visually appealing web experiences.

I'm excited about learning new techniques, technology, and skills to Become a better Developer and for the satisfaction granted by materialising an idea

### Other

- Won 2 awards including best UX at HackSussex 2018, an annual hackathon, working as the frontend dev on a location based chatroom with the goal of helping lonely students find new friends.
  The project used: HTML, SCSS, NodeJS, and Twillio's web-chat API
- Volunteered at HackSussex 2017

#### Skills \_

#### Front-End UI/UX Workflow Other

HTML
CSS/SCSS/
LESS
JavaScript

Wireframing
Prototyping
Adobe XD &
Adobe CC
User stories

GitHub Agile/Scrum

PHP MVC Python Django

Experience

### Junior Product Developer (Frontend Web Developer) ReedPop | Brighton | July 2020 - December 2020

Working as a Junior Frontend Web developer I maintained and updated an array of different sites, including Eurogamer.net and RockPaperShotgun.com, across a variety of platforms; PHP MVC, Wordpress, Django, etc. I also helped to build all new digital events sites for very large digital only events such as PAX x EGX for which we had over 12 million impressions.

### Technical Operator The Edit\_ | Brighton | September 2019 - July 2020

Working in television postproduction, helping with assistant editing and technical support, with a broad number of responsibilities and a variety of challenges daily in a high pressure environment as part of a small highly synergistic team.

## Live Video Production (Part time) University of Sussex | Brighton | January 2019 - April 2019

Working on open days in the Engineering & Informatics department, helping to operate a full live television broadcast studio, broadcasting talks given by lecturers to guests of prospective students

### Education

### Computing for Digital Media (BSc hons) University of Sussex

A three year course including modules: Web 3D Applications, Human-Computer Interaction, Technology Enhanced Learning, and Software Engineering.

### BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma IT

A two year A-level equivalent IT course